<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Geek Quote</string>
    <string name="quotefield">Type your quote here.</string>
    <string name="quotebutton">Add Quote</string>
    <string name="editquote">Edit Quote</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="refresh">Refresh</string>
    <string name="add_quote_finished">Quote sent to the server</string>
    <string name="refresh_quote_finished">Refresh successfull</string>
    <string name="refresh_quote_error_timedout">Connection timed out</string>
    <string name="refresh_quote_error_connrefused">Cannot connect to host</string>
    <string name="refresh_quote_error_json">Error during JSON parsing</string>
    <string name="refresh_quote_error_unknown">Unknown exception raised</string>
    <string-array name="quotes">
        <item>Today, I was given a bottle of vitamins that are supposed to help your memory. I forgot them at home. FML</item>
        <item>Today, I thought it would be funny to scare my dad for once, since he has scared me for fun dozens of times. It would have been funny, had he not punched me in the face. FML</item>
        <item>Today, I was walking to the bus in my favorite jeans, and I felt a uncontrollable itch in my leg. I scratched and it went away, but then I felt something moving on my leg. I hadn\'t worn my jeans in so long that a spider had decided to make it a nest. FML</item>
        <item>Today, I was at my girlfriend\'s house for the first time. I cracked a joke that offended her, so she gave me the silent treatment. I had to pee, and since she wouldn\'t tell me where the bathroom was, I went to look for it. I walked in on her parents making love. FML</item>
        <item>Today, while on trial for a desperately needed new job, I tripped crossing a road with my would-be manager. I twisted my ankle, and he had to carry me across the road and call a taxi for me to go home. FML</item>
        <item>Today, I accused a student in my class of getting his dad to do his homework. It turns out that his dad died 2 years ago. FML</item>
        <item>Today, my hay-fever started. I\'m five months pregnant, and every time I cough, sneeze or blow my nose I either fart or wet myself. FML</item>
        <item>Today, I was boarding a plane and a woman\'s bag started to fall. In the spur of the moment I thrust my arm up to catch it. I didn\'t catch the bag, but I did catch her boob. I had to sit next to her for the rest of the flight. FML</item>
        <item>Today, my husband and I got into a fight because I refused to let him use my finger nail to clean the plaque off his teeth. FML</item>
        <item>Today, I was locked out of my house and had to pee. I waited an hour for my boyfriend to come home. When I saw him pull into the driveway, I peed myself in excitement. FML</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>